Guide to the Daniel C. Roper Papers, 1860-1958 RL.01106
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical, 1927-1943, undated (bulk 1933-1938)
  - Fertich, Roscoe, 1934-1938 (Box 8)
  - Feuchtwanger, Joseph, 1928-1933 (Box 8)
  - Few, William P., 1928-1938 (Box 8)
  - Fg-Fl, 1928-1938 (Box 8)
  - Field, Robert M., 1932-1937 (Box 8)
  - Filene, Edward A., 1933-1937 (Box 8)
  - Filene, Lincoln, 1933-1938 (Box 8)
  - Fisheries, Bureau of, 1934-1938 (Box 8)
  - FitzHenry, Louis, 1933 (Box 8)
  - Flax production, 1933-1936 (Box 8)
  - Florida State Bar Association, 1934-1935 (Box 8)
  - Florida vacations, 1934-1942 (Box 8)
  - Flowers, R. L., 1928-1938 (Box 8)
  - Fm-Fr, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1929 (Box 8)
  - Foreign and Domestic Commerce, Bureau of, 1935-1938, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Foreign Service: Retirement Bill, 1938 (Box 8)
  - Foreign Trade:
    - 1933-1938 (Box 8)
    - Reports (George N. Peek) (Box 8)
  - Foreign Trade Week, celebration of, 1936-1937 (Box 8)
  - Foreign Trade Zones, 1934-1937 (Box 8)
  - Fox, Marvin L., 1928-1934 (Box 8)
  - Francis, Clarence, 1937-1938 (Box 8)
  - Fraternities, undated (Box 8)
  - Frazier, Frank, 1928-1937 (Box 8)
  - Frazier, Virgil H., 1934-1938 (Box 8)
  - Freed, Allie S., 1935-1938 (Box 8)
  - Freeman, James E., 1933-1937 (Box 8)
  - Frensdorf, Edward, 1933-1935 (Box 8)
  - Friant, Julian N., 1936-1938 (Box 8)
  - Friday, David, 1928 (Box 8)
  - Fs-Fz, 1928-1938 (Box 8)
  - Fullilove, S.C., 1933 (Box 8)
  - Ga-Gf, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Gannon, Elizabeth, 1936-1937 (Box 9)
  - Gans, Issac, 1933-1937 (Box 9)
  - Gardiner, W. Gwynn, 1933-1938 (Box 9)
  - Garner, John N., 1930-1938 (Box 9)
  - Gasque, Allard H., 1928-1938 (Box 9)
  - Garver, Harry H., 1935-1937 (Box 9)
  - Gell, Harry J., 1934-1943 (Box 9)
  - Genealogy, 1929-1935 (Box 9)
  - Gentry, J. J., 1929-1937 (Box 9)
  - Gg-Gl, 1886-1943 (Box 9)
  - Gideons, bibles, 1936 (Box 9)
  - Gifts received by Roper, 1933-1938 (Box 9)
  - Gm-Gr, 1928-1943, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Gonzales, W. E., 1932-1937 (Box 9)
  - Gore, Robert H., 1933-1938 (Box 9)
  - Government reorganization, 1933 (Box 9)
  - Grain Futures Act, 1934-1935 (Box 9)
  - Grayson, Cary T., 1927-1938 (Box 9)
  - Great Lakes Exposition, 1936-1937 (Box 9)
  - Greensboro College, 1935-1937 (Box 9)
  - Greenwood, Moses, 1932-1937 (Box 9)
  - Gridiron Club, 1933-1938 (Box 9)
  - Gs-Gz, 1928-1943 (Box 9)
  - Guffey, Joseph F., 1936-1938 (Box 9)
  - Gundlach, E. T., 1928-1938 (Box 9)
  - Ha-Hf, 1928-1943, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Hackett, E. F., 1936-1938 (Box 9)
  - Hagner, Randall H. and Co., 1931 (Box 9)
  - Halsey, Edwin A., 1932-1938 (Box 9)
  - Haly, Percy, 1928-1937 (Box 9)
  - Hamer, Tom M., 1932-1938, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Hamer, William M., 1933-1935 (Box 9)
  - Hamilton, Norman R., 1934-1938 (Box 10)
  - Hamlin, Frank, T., 1928-1933 (Box 10)
  - Haney, Bert E., 1933 (Box 10)
  - Hansbrough, H. C., 1932 (Box 10)
  - Hardison, Robert B., 1934-1937 (Box 10)
  - Harmon, Nolan B., 1929-1935 (Box 10)
  - Harriman, W. Averell, 1933-1943 (Box 10)
  - Harris, Edwin S., 1932-1936 (Box 10)
  - Harris, Frederick Brown, 1929-1937 (Box 10)
  - Harrison, William Henry, 1937-1938 (Box 10)
  - Harvey, Richard, 1928-1933 (Box 10)
  - Hathaway, Minnie, 1928-1933 (Box 10)
  - Hawkins, Walter, 1934-1938 (Box 10)
  - Hay, Charles M., 1928-1943 (Box 10)
  - Hecht, R. S., 1936-1937 (Box 10)
  - Heflin, J. Thomas, 1934-1938 (Box 10)
  - Heimann, Henry H., 1933-1943 (Box 10)
  - Helium reserves, 1937 (Box 10)
  - Hentz, Henry and Company, 1929-1938 (Box 10)
  - Hereley, D. G. "Ted," 1933-1938 (Box 10)
  - Hereley, Hannah M., 1932-1937 (Box 10)
  - Herman, Raphael, 1928-1938 (Box 10)
  - Hg-Hl, 1928-1943 (Box 10)
  - High, Stanley, 1934-1937 (Box 10)
  - Hildreth, Melvin D., 1927-1943 (Box 10)
  - Hill, John Wesley, 1933-1936 (Box 10)
  - Hindenburg Accident, 1936-1937 (Box 10)
  - Hm-Hr, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Hobbs, Franklin W., 1933-1943 (Box 10)
  - Hodges, Edward P., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Holt, Hamilton, 1928-1943 (Box 10)
  - Hopkins, Harry, 1933-1938 (Box 10)
  - Hotels, 1928-1938 (Box 10)
  - House, E. M., 1919-1938 (Box 10)
  - Housing, 1933-1938 (Box 10)
  - Houston, Herbert S., 1933-1938 (Box 10)
  - Howard, Clinton N., 1929-1937 (Box 10)
  - Howe, Louis McHenry, 1931-1936 (Box 10)
  - Howell, Clark, 1933-1937 (Box 10)
  - Hoyt, James A., 1930-1933 (Box 10)
  - Hs-Hz, 1928-1943 (Box 11)
  - Hull, Cordell, 1927-1943 (Box 11)
  - Hurley, Edward N., 1933 (Box 11)
  - Hurrey, Clarence B., 1932-1939 (Box 11)
  - Hutchinson, Forney, 1932-1937 (Box 11)
  - Hutchinson, J. E., 1933-1936 (Box 11)
  - I, 1928-1943 (Box 11)
  - Ickes, Harold L., 1932-1938 (Box 11)
  - Inauguration, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Insurance, 1932-1938 (Box 11)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1920(2 vols. and 1 folder) (Box 11)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1933 (Box 11)
  - Irey, Elmer L., 1932-1938 (Box 11)
  - Ja-Jl, 1928-1938 (Box 11)
  - Jackson, Burris, 1936-1938 (Box 11)
  - Jackson, Charles E., 1932-1937 (Box 11)
  - Jackson Day Dinner, 1936-1938 (Box 11)
  - Jacobs, Harry L., 1933-1937 (Box 11)
  - Jamieson, W. D., 1928-1938 (Box 11)
  - Japanese Economic Mission, 1937, May 11-June 16 (Box 11)
  - Jefferson Islands Club, 1934-1937 (Box 11)
  - Jefferson Memorial, 1936-1938 (Box 11)
  - Jenckes, Virginia E., 1933-1936 (Box 11)
  - Jennifer, William, 1933-1937 (Box 11)
  - Jewelers of the United States, volume, 1917(?) (Box 11)
  - Jm-Jz, 1928-1938 (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Hugh S., 1933-1935 (Box 11)
  - Johnson, J. Monroe, Assistant Secretary of Commerce, 1935-1938 (Box 11)
  - Jones, Jessie H., 1928-1938 (Box 12)
  - Julian, W. A., 1928-1938 (Box 12)
  - Justice Department, 1933-1938 (Box 12)
  - Ka-Kf, 1928-1943 (Box 12)
  - Kaltenborn, H. V., 1935-1936 (Box 12)
  - Kempler, William T., 1933-1938 (Box 12)
  - Kendall, Henry P., 1933-1938 (Box 12)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., 1936-1938 (Box 12)
  - Kern, Paul B., 1938 (Box 12)
  - Kernahan Campaign, evangelism, 1930 (Box 12)
  - Kg-Kl, 1933-1938 (Box 12)
  - King, W. L. MacKenzie, 1938-1943 (Box 12)
  - Kip, Frederic E., 1935-1936 (Box 12)
  - Kiwanis Club, 1934-1936 (Box 12)
  - Klien, Ernest L., 1933-1943 (Box 12)
  - Klinck, J. C., 1935-1937 (Box 12)
  - Km-Kz, 1928-1943 (Box 12)
  - Knapp, Frank F., 1929-1936 (Box 12)
  - Knight, Peter O., 1935-1936 (Box 12)
  - Knoxville, Tenn., tariff controversy, 1931 (Box 12)
  - Kraft, Herman F., 1933-1938 (Box 12)
  - Kroner, Hayes, 1928-1936 (Box 12)
  - Kuhn, Oliver Owen, 1933-1937 (Box 12)
  - La-Lf, 1928-1943, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Labor Department, 1933-1938 (Box 12)
  - Lamar, Lucy, 1933-1937 (Box 12)
  - Lambeth, William A., 1928-1943 (Box 12)
  - Lamport, Sam C., 1933-1937 (Box 12)
  - Landon, Alf M., 1936campaign (Box 12)
  - Lane, Alex M., 1933-1938 (Box 12)
  - Lane, Julius J., 1928-1938 (Box 12)
  - Latimer, J. Austin, 1936-1938 (Box 12)
  - Lauck, W. Jett, 1932 (Box 12)
  - Law, William A., 1933-1936 (Box 12)
  - Laws, Bolitha J., 1928-1938 (Box 12)
  - Lawson, Martin E., 1929-1936 (Box 13)
  - Lawton, J. J., 1932-1938 (Box 13)
  - League of Nations Association, 1928-1938 (Box 13)
  - Leete, Frederick D., 1934-1938 (Box 13)
  - Legge, Alexander, 1929-1936 (Box 13)
  - Legislation, U.S. Congress, 1933-1938 (Box 13)
  - L'Enfant, Pierre Charles, Memorial, 1928-1930 (Box 13)
  - Letts, John C., 1929-1936 (Box 13)
  - Lewine, Jerome, 1929 (Box 13)
  - Lewis, J. Hamilton, 1932-1936 (Box 13)
  - Lg-Ll, 1928-1943 (Box 13)
  - Lightfoot, M. D., 1928-1929 (Box 13)
  - Lightle, James F., 1932 (Box 13)
  - Liquor Control Committee, 1933, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Lm-Lr, 1928-1943 (Box 13)
  - Long, Breckinridge, 1933-1937 (Box 13)
  - Long, Richard Henry, 1928-1943 (Box 13)
  - Loose, Ella, 1935-1943 (Box 13)
  - Lord, J. A., 1928-1938 (Box 13)
  - Love, Thomas B., 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Lowson, Frank, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Ls-Lz, 1928-1943 (Box 13)
  - Ludlow, Louis, 1928-1938 (Box 13)
  - Ma-Mf, 1928-1943, 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Ma-Mf, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - MacFadden, Bernarr, 1934-1937 (Box 14)
  - MacRae, Hugh, 1928-1936 (Box 14)
  - Mahany, Rowland B., 1928-1932 (Box 14)
  - Mahoney, William V., 1936 (Box 14)
  - Malone, Paul B., 1933-1937 (Box 14)
  - Maloney, Thomas, 1933-1938 (Box 14)
  - Marine Inspection and Navigation, Bureau of, 1937-1938 (Box 14)
  - Maritime Commission, United States, 1936-1938 (Box 14)
  - Marshall, Rowland S., 1933-1936 (Box 14)
  - Marshall, Stuart B., 1932-1933 (Box 14)
  - Martin, A. E., 1932-1936 (Box 14)
  - Martin, George, 1933-1935 (Box 14)
  - Martin, Harry, 1902-1937 (Box 14)
  - Martin, Rex, 1934-1937 (Box 14)
  - Masons, 1929-1938 (Box 14)
  - Mattern, James J., 1937 (Box 14)
  - Matthews, Ben C., 1933-1937 (Box 14)
  - Mattox, E. Tilden, 1935-1937 (Box 14)
  - Maybank, Burnet, 1936-1943 (Box 14)
  - McAdoo, William Gibbs, 1916-1939, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - McArdle, Ruskin, 1932-1938 (Box 14)
  - McArdle, Willett, 1934-1935 (Box 14)
  - McCall, Chester H., 1933-1938 (Box 14)
  - McColl, Delle Roper, 1929-1937 (Box 14)
  - McColl, Eulah, 1928-1938 (Box 14)
  - McColl, J. B., 1932-1935 (Box 14)
  - McConihe, Malcolm S., 1933-1937 (Box 14)
  - McCormick Vance C., 1928-1940 (Box 14)
  - McCormick, Willoughby M., 1931-1932 (Box 14)
  - McCulloch, J. E., 1928-1938 (Box 14)
  - McDonald, Capt. J. J., 1917-1932 (Box 14)
  - McGrath, John J., 1933-1938 (Box 14)
  - McGurn, Arthur J., 1936 (Box 14)
  - McIntyre, Marvin H., 1933-1943 (Box 14)
  - McKee, William A., 1933-1937 (Box 14)
  - McKellar, Kenneth, 1934-1938 (Box 14)
  - McKenzie, William N., Sr., 1928-1938 (Box 14)
  - McKenzie, William N., Jr., 1932-1938 (Box 14)
  - McLaurin, Sidney L., 1932-1940 (Box 14)
  - McLean, Angus W., 1928-1937 (Box 14)
  - McLendon and Hedrick, lawyers, 1928 (Box 14)
  - McLeod, F. H., 1933-1936 (Box 14)
  - McMillan, E. J., 1933-1938 (Box 14)
  - McMillan, Thomas S. 1937-1938 (Box 14)
  - McMorran, C. W., 1935-1938 (Box 14)
  - McNeal, George H., 1929-1936 (Box 14)
  - McNeil, Archibald, 1933-1936 (Box 14)
  - McRae, A. C., Jr., 1934-1938 (Box 14)
  - McSwain, J. J., 1932-1936 (Box 14)
  - Mead, George H., 1933-1938 (Box 14)
  - Meekins, Lynn W., 1936-1938 (Box 14)
  - Mellon, Andrew W., 1928 (Box 14)
  - Memberships, miscellaneous, 1933-1938 (Box 15)
  - Memoranda, miscellaneous, 1932-1938 (Box 15)
  - Merchant Marine, 1933-1938 (Box 15)
  - Meredith, E. T., 1920-1929 (Box 15)
  - Merger of D.C. utilities, 1932 (Box 15)
  - Messages, 1933-1938, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Methodist Church, 1929-1943, undated, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church, South:
    - Committee on Appeals, 1931-1932 (Box 15)
    - General conference, 1930 (Box 15)
    - Judicial Council, 1928-1929 (Box 15)
  - Mg-Ml, 1928-1943 (Box 15)
  - Michelson, Charles, 1932-1938 (Box 15)
  - Middleton, Hugh Calhoun, 1933-1935 (Box 15)
  - Miles, Vincent, 1933-1938 (Box 15)
  - Millar, A. C., 1933-1938 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Douglas, 1936-1937 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Hugh, 1933 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Izetta Jewell, 1933-1937 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Justin, 1932-1938 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Milton A. 1932-1935 (Box 15)
  - Milton, George Fort, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Mitchell, Ewing Y., 1928-1934 (Box 15)
  - Mm-Mr, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Moehlenpah, H. A., 1929-1933 (Box 15)
  - Moley, Raymond, 1933-1935 (Box 15)
  - Monopolies, 1937-1938 (Box 15)
  - Montgomery, Mabel, 1933-1937 (Box 15)
  - Moody, Alvin, 1928-1932 (Box 15)
  - Mooney, James D., 1933-1937 (Box 15)
  - Moore, Arthur J., 1936-1938 (Box 15)
  - Morgan, W. Forbes, 1932-1937 (Box 15)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, 1933-1937 (Box 15)
  - Morris, Ira Nelson, 1934-1938 (Box 15)
  - Morrison, Charles C., 1937 (Box 15)
  - Morrison, R. W., 1933-1938 (Box 15)
  - Morro Castle, steamboat sinking, 1934 (Box 15)
  - Morse, V. D., 1928-1935 (Box 15)
  - Motion pictures, 1933-1938 (Box 16)
  - Mott, John R., 1932 (Box 16)
  - Mount Vernon Place Methodist Episcopal Church, South, 1928-1938, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Moyer, J. S., 1937-1938 (Box 16)
  - Ms-Mz, 1928-1943 (Box 16)
  - Murphy, Frederick E., 1934-1937 (Box 16)
  - Murphy, Louis J., 1932-1937 (Box 16)
  - Murrell, John M., Mr. and Mrs., 1933-1938 (Box 16)
  - Na-Nf, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Narcotics, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - National Advisory Council, 1931-1935 (Box 16)
  - National Benefit Life Insurance Company, 1931-1938, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - National Business Show, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - National Conference of Jews and Christians, 1931-1933 (Box 16)
  - National Emergency Council, 1933-1936 (Box 16)
  - National Institute of Public Affairs, 1934-1938 (Box 16)
  - National organizations, miscellaneous, 1930-1938 (Box 16)
  - National Preaching Mission, 1936 (Box 16)
  - National Recovery Administration, 1933-1937, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - National Safety Council, 1934-1935 (Box 16)
  - National University, 1935-1938 (Box 16)
  - National Woman's Democratic Law Enforcement League, 1929 (Box 16)
  - Neblett, William H., 1934-1936 (Box 16)
  - Negroes, 1933-1938 (Box 16)
  - Nesbit, Scott, 1932-1935 (Box 16)
  - Neutrality, United States, 1936-1937 (Box 16)
  - New England Society of South Carolina, 1934 (Box 16)
  - Newspapers, magazines, etc., 1933-1938, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Newton, Byron R., 1928-1938 (Box 17)
  - New York World's Fair, 1937-1939 (Box 17)
  - Ng-Nz, 1928-1943 (Box 17)
  - Niles, Frank B., 1927-1932 (Box 17)
  - Nippert, Alfred K., 1932-1943 (Box 17)
  - Noyes, Theodore W., 1937-1938 (Box 17)
  - Nunn, C. S., 1928-1935 (Box 17)
  - Nutt, L. G., 1928-1935 (Box 17)
  - Oa-Ol, 1926-1941 (Box 17)
  - Obici, A., 1934-1938 (Box 17)
  - O'Connell, William L., 1935-1936 (Box 17)
  - O'Connor, J. F. T., 1933-1938 (Box 17)
  - Oleson, Anna Dickie, 1932-1937 (Box 17)
  - Om-Oz, 1926-1941 (Box 17)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa (Duke University), 1929-1936 (Box 17)
  - Owen, Robert L., 1932-1938 (Box 17)
  - Owen, Ruth Bryan, 1929-1935 (Box 17)
  - Oxford Group, 1934-1936 (Box 17)
  - Pa-Pf, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Palaver Club, 1931-1937 (Box 17)
  - Palmer, A. Mitchell, 1932-1936 (Box 17)
  - Parker, Walter, 1935-1938 (Box 17)
  - Patent Centennial, 1936, Nov. 23 (Box 17)
  - Patent Office and patents, miscellaneous, 1935-1938 (Box 17)
  - Patterson, Jean Rushmore, 1932 (Box 17)
  - Patterson, Richard C., Jr., 1935-1938 (Box 17)
  - Payer, Harry F., 1933-1939 (Box 17)
  - Peabody, George Foster, 1932-1937 (Box 17)
  - Peacock, J. Craig, 1932-1937 (Box 17)
  - Pearlstine, S.S., 1934-1938 (Box 17)
  - Penn Club, 1935 (Box 17)
  - Perkins, Frances, 1933-1937 (Box 17)
  - Perkins, W. R., 1932-1933 (Box 17)
  - Personnel (miscellaneous), 1933-1938 (Box 17)
  - Peters, Andrew J., 1917-1938 (Box 17)
  - Peters, James W. S., 1933-1937 (Box 18)
  - Pg-Pl, 1928-1943 (Box 18)
  - Philadelphia Convention, 1936 (Box 18)
  - Phillips, G. Z., 1928-1936 (Box 18)
  - Pickett, Deets, 1927-1937 (Box 18)
  - Pinci, A. R., 1932-1940 (Box 18)
  - Pleasantaire Corporation, 1937 (Box 18)
  - Pm-Pr, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Poe, Clarence, 1933-1938 (Box 18)
  - Poland Spring House, Maine, 1932-1937 (Box 18)
  - Poling, Daniel A., 1930-1937 (Box 18)
  - Politics: 1932 Democratic National Campaign, 1932, 10 folders (Box 18)
  - Politics:
    - 1936 Democratic National Campaign, 1936 (Box 18)
    - 1938 Democratic National Campaign, 1938 (Box 18)
    - Democratic Party, 1928-1938, 6 folders (Box 18)
  - Pomerene, Atlee, 1928-1937 (Box 18)
  - Portraits, 1934-1936 (Box 18)
  - Postmaster General: (Box 19)
    - Free Delivery Service, 1860-1911 (Box 19)
    - Precedents and Practice, 1915 (Box 19)
  - Pratt, G. W., 1928-1938 (Box 20)
  - President's birthday ball, 1935-1938 (Box 20)
  - President's Cup Regatta, 1934-1938 (Box 20)
  - Press, 1936-1938 (Box 20)
  - Press Club, 1932-1938 (Box 20)
  - Press Conferences, 1934-1938 (Box 20)
  - Press Releases (Department of Commerce), 1933-1938, 10 folders (Box 20)
  - Press, miscellaneous, undated (Box 20)
  - Price, Jesse D., 1935 (Box 20)
  - Price, John W., 1927-1938 (Box 20)
  - Price, Katherine Z., 1935-1937 (Box 20)
  - Price, Theodore H. 1928-1935 (Box 20)
  - Prohibition, 1927-1936, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Prohibition, 1932 Campaign, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Prohibition, (law enforcement), 1928-1929 (Box 20)
  - Ps-Pz, 1928-1938 (Box 20)
  - Public Works Administration, 1933-1938 (Box 20)
  - Publicity Bureau, Department of Commerce (H. R. Daniel), 1938 (Box 20)
  - Purdy, E. A., 1932-1937 (Box 20)
  - Q, 1932-1938 (Box 20)
  - Questionnaires, miscellaneous (Roper's responses), 1933-1938 (Box 20)
  - Quinn, Stanley J., 1932-1935 (Box 21)
  - Ra-Rf, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Radio (addresses and miscellaneous), 1928-1938 (Box 21)
  - Railroads, 1933-1938 (Box 21)
  - Rainey, Henry T., 1928-1935 (Box 21)
  - Randolph, Hollis N., 1928-1938 (Box 21)
  - Rankin, William H., 1933-1938 (Box 21)
  - Raper, C. L., 1932-1943 (Box 21)
  - Rayburn, Sam, 1933-1938 (Box 21)
  - Recommendations (miscellaneous), 1937-1938 (Box 21)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1932-1938 (Box 21)
  - Reisner, Christian F., 1930-1939 (Box 21)
  - Religion and religious groups, 1932-1938 (Box 21)
  - Religion and Welfare Recovery, 1934-1937 (Box 21)
  - Reorganization of U.S. Government Departments, 1933-1937 (Box 21)
  - Reports (cross-references), 1935-1938 (Box 21)
  - Revere, C. T., 1932-1939 (Box 21)
  - Rg-Rl, 1928-1943 (Box 21)
  - Richberg, Donald, 1935-1939 (Box 21)
  - Rippy, J. Fred, 1932-1937 (Box 21)
  - Rm-Rr, 1928-1943, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Robert, Lawrence Wood, Jr., 1933-1939 (Box 21)
  - Roberts, Coleman W., 1934-1937 (Box 21)
  - Roberts, George M., 1933-1938 (Box 21)
  - Robins, William L., 1928-1939 (Box 21)
  - Robinson, David, 1937 (Box 21)
  - Robinson, Elsie, 1932-1934 (Box 21)
  - Robinson, Joseph T., 1933-1937 (Box 21)
  - Rockefeller, John D., 1934-1937 (Box 21)
  - Rogers, Elmer E., 1932-1939 (Box 21)
  - Rogers, James Harvey, 1932-1939 (Box 21)
  - Rogers, Sallie C., 1933 (Box 21)
  - Rogers Will, 1933-1938 (Box 21)
  - Rollins College, Winter Park, Florida, 1928-1937 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1933-1939 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.:
    - 1919-1943, undated (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous memoranda, 1933-1938, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Secretary Louis McH. Howe, 1933-1934 (Box 21)
  - Roosevelt, James, 1933-1938 (Box 22)
  - Root, Nelly Hall, 1928-1937 (Box 22)
  - Roper, A. Kent, 1932-1933 (Box 22)
  - Roper, Alvin W., 1928 (Box 22)
  - Roper, Daniel C.:
    - Biographical, 1913-1938, undated (Box 22)
    - Personal, 1928-1939 (Box 22)
  - Roper, Daniel C. Jr., 1920-1938, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Roper, Harry McK., 1928-1938 (Box 22)
  - Roper, Jack C., 1928-1938 (Box 22)
  - Roper, James Hunter, 1930-1938 (Box 22)
  - Roper, John Wesley, 1929-1937 (Box 22)
  - Roper, Lou McKenzie:
    - A-Z, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Roper, Richard Fred, 1928-1937, 3 folders (Box 22)
  - Roper, T. W., 1928-1932 (Box 22)
  - Roper family, 1886-1943, undated (Box 22)
  - Roper genealogy, family history, etc., 1933-1938 (Box 22)
  - Roper residence, Washington, D.C., 1925-1938, undated (Box 22)
  - Roper, miscellaneous, 1933-1938 (Box 22)
  - Rosser, C. M., 1930-1937 (Box 22)
  - Rothchild, Meyer D., 1932-1936 (Box 22)
  - Rowe, L. S., 1928-1943 (Box 22)
  - Rs-Rz, 1928-1943 (Box 23)
  - Rukeyser, Merryle S., 1933-1938 (Box 23)
  - Russell, Charles Edward, 1935-1937 (Box 23)
  - Russell, William J., 1928-1939 (Box 23)
  - Russia, miscellaneous, 1933-1937 (Box 23)
  - Rustin, John W., 1937-1939 (Box 23)
  - Sa-Sf, 1930-1939, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - Sabella, Ricardo H., 1936-1937 (Box 23)
  - St. Clair, Labert, 1933-1939 (Box 23)
  - Saltzman, Charles McK., 1933-1938, undated (Box 23)
  - Salvation Army, 1933-1938 (Box 23)
  - Sanders, Jared Y., 1932-1933 (Box 23)
  - Sanford, Fred L., 1932-1943 (Box 23)
  - Scarborough, J. H., 1933-1938 (Box 23)
  - Seagrave, Arthur E., 1935-1938 (Box 23)
  - Seeligson, Arthur A., 1932-1929 (Box 23)
  - Seibels, Edwin G., 1935-1939 (Box 23)
  - Sells, Cato, 1930-1939 (Box 23)
  - Senatorial campaigns, contributions, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Sg-Sl, 1930-1943, undated, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Shaver, C. L., 1930-1936 (Box 23)
  - Shaw, Albert, 1936-1939 (Box 23)
  - Shaw, Alex C., 1930-1933 (Box 23)
  - Shepherd, Jesse L., 1937-1939 (Box 23)
  - Sheppard, Morris, 1933-1939 (Box 23)
  - Sherwood, Carlton M., 1933-1943 (Box 23)
  - Shinn, Earl Whittier, 1938-1939 (Box 23)
  - Shipping, 1934-1937 (Box 23)
  - Shoemaker, Samuel M., 1937-1938 (Box 23)
  - Sholtz, David, 1934-1939 (Box 23)
  - Showalter, William J., 1930-1933 (Box 23)
  - Shuff, John L., 1930-1939 (Box 23)
  - Shure, Ralph G., 1931-1936, undated (Box 23)
  - Shutts, Frank B., 1935-1939 (Box 23)
  - Sibley, Harper, 1936-1939 (Box 23)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity, 1932-1938, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Silverman, Samuel W., 1932-1938, undated (Box 23)
  - Simmons, Furnifold M., 1929-1938 (Box 23)
  - Sinnot, John F., 1934-1937 (Box 23)
  - Slemp, C. Bascom, 1930-1937 (Box 23)
  - Sloane, George A., 1935-1938 (Box 23)
  - Sm-Sr, 1886-1939, undated, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Small, John H., 1930-1937 (Box 24)
  - Small Business Men's Conference, 1938 (Box 24)
  - Smith, Arthur C., 1933-1937 (Box 24)
  - Smith, Elizabeth, 1932-1935 (Box 24)
  - Smith, Ellison D., 1932-1938 (Box 24)
  - Smith, Frank, 1933-1938 (Box 24)
  - Smith, Fred B., 1933-1937 (Box 24)
  - Smith, Rembert G., 1935-1937 (Box 24)
  - Smith, Tom K., 1938-1943 (Box 24)
  - Smith, W. Angie, 1934-1937 (Box 24)
  - Smith, Willis, 1932-1937 (Box 24)
  - Snell, Arthur V., 1932-1933 (Box 24)
  - Société Amonyme des Minerais, 1939 (Box 24)
  - Sommers, H. A., 1934-1936 (Box 24)
  - Soong, T. V., 1933-1940 (Box 24)
  - South Carolina, miscellaneous, 1932-1939, undated (Box 24)
  - Southeastern Development Board, 1934 (Box 24)
  - Southern Society of Washington, 1930-1937 (Box 24)
  - Sowell, Ashley B., 1934-1943 (Box 24)
  - Spivey, Ludd M., 1930-1937 (Box 24)
  - Splawn, Walter M. W., 1930-1937 (Box 24)
  - SS President Hoover, 1938 (Box 24)
  - Ss-Sz, 1930-1943, undated, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Stackhouse, M. Steed, 1932-1937, undated (Box 24)
  - Stackhouse, T. B., 1926-1939, undated (Box 24)
  - Stackhouse, Texie, 1933, undated (Box 24)
  - Stackhouse, Wade, 1932-1938 (Box 24)
  - Stackhouse, Walter F., 1930-1939 (Box 24)
  - Stackhouse, Will, 1930-1943 (Box 24)
  - Standards, Bureau of, 1934 (Box 24)
  - State Department, 1933-1938, undated (Box 24)
  - Stettinius, Edward R., Jr., 1933-1943 (Box 24)
  - Steuart, William M., 1930-1933 (Box 24)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1935-1938 (Box 24)
  - Stone, Alfred H., 1932-1934 (Box 24)
  - Stover, James D., 1932-1935 (Box 24)
  - Stuart, R. Douglas, 1937-1939 (Box 24)
  - Sulzer, William, 1933-1939 (Box 24)
  - Summaries of newspaper editorials about Roper, 1933-1936 (Box 24)
  - Sweet, E. M., 1933-1943 (Box 24)
  - Sweet, William E., 1930-1934 (Box 24)
  - Ta-Tf, 1887-1939 (Box 25)
  - Tariff, 1932 campaign, 1932 (Box 25)
  - Taussig, F. W., 1918-1934 (Box 25)
  - Taxes, miscellaneous, 1919-1939, undated (Box 25)
  - Taylor, James H., 1928-1930 (Box 25)
  - Telegrams, 1931-1932 (Box 25)
  - Tg-Tz, 1919-1939 (Box 25)
  - Travel expenses, 1932-1933 (Box 25)
  - Traxler, David B., 1928-1939 (Box 25)
  - Trimble, South, Jr., 1931-1932 (Box 25)
  - U, 1928-1932 (Box 25)
  - U.S. Constitution, celebration, 1935-1937 (Box 25)
  - U.S. Post Office, 1932-1938 (Box 25)
  - Unemployment relief, 1934-1938 (Box 25)
  - University Club, 1930-1933 (Box 25)
  - V, 1928-1939 (Box 25)
  - Vacations, 1930-1932 (Box 25)
  - Wa-Wf, 1928-1939 (Box 25)
  - Walker, Frank C., 1932-1939 (Box 25)
  - Wallace, Hugh, 1919-1932 (Box 25)
  - Walter, William E., 1933-1936 (Box 25)
  - Washington Criminal Justice Association, 1939 (Box 25)
  - Washington Federation of Churches (W. L. Darby), 1932 (Box 25)